翻译   杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译   香茗小焙
翻译   小饭
翻译   某羽
翻译   肉松富士
翻译   草草
时间轴   兜兜兜爹
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
鸣谢   忙成狗的网飞
鸣谢   阿小小海
特效   草草
校对   草草
总监   草草
纸牌屋
第三季  第十二集
爱荷华州
邓巴爱荷华州得梅因市大本营
民调显示邓巴在党团会议前支持率稍领先于总统
如果今天是总统大选  你会把票投给谁
安德伍德竞选宣传计划挨家挨户拜访爱荷华州居民
空军一号将于今日在爱荷华州降落
邓巴好感点
领导力
凝聚力
号召力
信念
2016  安德伍德
证据增加  美军海豹突击队
参与约旦河谷行动
距爱荷华州党团会议只有一周
With just one week to go before the Iowa caucuses,
最新盖洛普民调显示
the latest Gallup poll has
邓巴以45比39领先6个百分点
Dunbar ahead by six points, 45 to 39,
仍有16%的人尚未决定
with 16 percent still undecided.
大选在即  尚未决定的人还真不少
That's a lot of undecideds so close to election day.
邓巴在这里好感度极高
Dunbar has incredibly high favorability numbers here,
比安德伍德总统的要高得多
much higher than President Underwood's,
但与我交谈的许多爱荷华州人士
but I have spoken with many Iowans
对她经验的匮乏仍存有顾虑
who have doubts about her lack of experience
同时还担心她将来是否能战胜一位
and whether she'll be able to stand up to a Republican candidate
资历优秀的共和党候选人
with a substantial record.
即便如此  考虑到她从未参加过竞选
Even so, the fact that she's still the frontrunner,
-却仍是竞选领跑者  -真了不起
- having never run for office. - It's extraordinary.
杰姬·夏普的支持举足轻重
Jackie Sharp's endorsement was a big coup.
真的影响了她在女性选民中的支持率
It really helped her numbers with women.
我们希望您能在活动中更积极一些
We want you to have a much more active role during the events.
您先开始  介绍总统
You'll go first, introduce the president,
至始至终跟他在一起
stay with him the entire time,
然后参与问答环节
and then participate in the Q and A.
我实在不该回答问题
I really shouldn't be answering questions.
弗朗西斯才是候选人
Francis is the candidate.
事实是  你的好感度是我的二倍
Well, the truth is, your favorables are double what mine are,
那我们就给人们他们想要的吧
so let's give the people what they want.
好吧  如果你觉得这样有帮助的话
Well, if you think it will help.
肯定会的
I know it will.
你们准备演讲稿了吗  有没有问题清单
Do you have a speech prepared? Do you have issue papers?
一切都在会议室里
Everything is in the conference room.
那我们就开始吧
Let's get started, then.
您有没有看过那个清单
Have you had a chance to go over the list...
雷米的接替者的名单
of replacements for Remy?
我现在不能考虑那个
Oh, I can't focus on that right now.
我得先考虑爱荷华州
I need to get through Iowa first.
我要推荐个人  先生  那人不在名单上
Well, I have a suggestion, sir, that's not on the list.
谁
Who?
我
Me.
赛斯  作为新闻主管  你的价值无法估量
Seth, you're invaluable as a comm director.
就是因为这个  先生
Well, that's just it, sir.
您需要个媒体专家替您掌舵
You need a media expert at the helm.
我们处在选举周期之内呢
We're in an election cycle.
-一切都和公共形象密切相关  -赛斯
- Everything's about perception. - Seth--
我想将政策和新闻团队完美融合
I want to integrate the policy and the press teams.
我希望与内阁成员及机构首脑合作
I want to work with cabinet members and agency heads
按我们的政纲调整每份公开声明
on gearing every public statement towards our platform.
动员国会中的《美就法》盟友
Mobilize our AmWorks allies in Congress.
一份关于未来立法的承诺表
A commitment list for future's legislations,
不仅是支持
not just simple endorsements.
这里面详细写了
Look, this outlines in detail
我担任您幕僚长会采取的行动
what I would like to do as your Chief of Staff.
我只求您考虑考虑
All I ask is that you consider it.
我当然会的  谢谢你  赛斯
Well, of course I will. Thank you, Seth.
我很感激你这么花心思
I appreciate you putting so much time into this.
谢谢您  先生
Thank you, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
罗伯特
Robert.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm running late.
我们从爱荷华州回来时天气不太好
We hit some weather on the way back from Iowa.
我感谢你亲自过来
I appreciate your coming here in person.
尤其在这...最后冲刺阶段
Especially during the... final rush.
为了你什么都行  罗伯特
Anything for you, Robert.
请坐
Have a seat.
多谢
Oh, thank you.
这也好  我也能跟孩子们待一会儿
And, you know, it's good. I get a few hours with the kids.
回到这儿感觉如何
So how does it feel to be back here?
我得承认  我是有点怀念
I have to admit, I miss it a little.
顺说  你戈弗雷诉肯特案的异议提得真好
Your dissent on Godfrey v. Kent was brilliant, by the way.
我的手下  是他们写的
My clerks. They wrote it.
每个字都是
Every word.
所以现在是时候了
So it's time.
露丝说是  但我在她开口前就知道了
Ruth says it is, but I knew before she said anything.
-你准备什么时候宣布  -很快
- When are you going to announce? - Soon.
但是我想先听你说同意
But I'd like you... to say yes first.
-同意什么  -接替我
- To what? - Replacing me.
我并不是病糊涂了
This isn't the disease speaking.
我并没有忘记你正在竞选总统
I haven't forgotten you're running for President.
但是安德伍德
But Underwood...
我肯定他会毫不犹豫地同意提名你
I'm sure he'd nominate you in a heartbeat.
我现在占上风  罗伯特  为什么要退出
I am the frontrunner, Robert. Why would I drop out?
因为这个职位是终身的
Because this position's for life.
安德伍德会输的
Underwood is going to lose.
你觉得他会轻易认输吗
You think he'll go down easily?
而且即使你拿到了提名  共和党...
And even if you get the nomination, the Republicans...
他们会生吞活剥了你
They'll... rip you apart.
我是决定性一票  我的位置很重要
I'm the swing vote. My seat is important.
你在这里可以产生长期的影响
You can make a lasting difference here.
他也是这么说的
That is exactly what he said.
他的动机不纯  是的
His motivations were atrocious, yes,
但他说的道理是对的
but his logic was sound.
看来你的头脑还像过去一样清醒  罗伯特
Your mind seems sharp as ever, Robert.
只是
Except...
只是我现在想不起来你叫什么
Except for the fact that I can't remember your name right now.
希瑟
Heather.
你能继续我未竟的事业吗  希瑟
Will you continue to do the work I've done, Heather?
我不能
I can't.
摸着良心说  我太希望能成功了
If I'm honest with myself, it's that I want this too much.
开始竞选前我根本没有意识到
I didn't realize it before I started running.
并不是我变了  罗伯特
It is not that I've changed, Robert,
我并不是被野心蒙蔽了双眼
that ambition has clouded anything.
而是我之前都没有意识到我注定该做什么
It is that I was blind to this until now, what I am meant to be.
我注定要成为美国总统
And I am meant to be President of the United States.
你们是不是都想先听克莱尔讲话
Wouldn't you all like to hear from Claire first?
谢谢
Thank you!
弗兰西斯和我十分感激你们能冒着严寒
Francis and I so appreciate you all coming out here
到这里来如此热情地欢迎我们
on such a cold day and welcoming us with such warmth!
回到爱荷华真是太好了
It's so good to be back in Iowa!
而且我能感觉到  有了你们的支持和热情
And I can feel it, with your support and enthusiasm,
我们毫无疑问会拿下这个州
there is no doubt that we are gonna take this state!
-你好  -晚上好
- Hello. - Good evening.
很高兴二位又能在我家留宿  总统先生
So pleased to have you staying with us again, Mr. President.
我们一向喜欢来这里
We always love coming here.
这是全爱荷华我们最喜欢的房子
It's our favorite house in all of Iowa.
-如果二位有什么需要  -非常感谢
- If you need anything... - Thank you very much.
-晚安  -祝你们睡个好觉
- Good night. - Have a good evening.
你今天表现十分出色
You were wonderful today.
他们非常喜欢你
They just adore you.
晚安
Good night.
请帮我接通汤姆·耶茨的电话
Yes, connect me with Tom Yates, please.
不  我等着
No, I'll hold.
总统先生
Mr. President?
剩下的部分呢
Where's the rest of it?
-你读了吗  -还没有
- Have you read it? - No, not yet.
我只拿到了第一章
Just this first chapter arrived.
请你先读一下  先生  然后我们再谈
Will you please read it first, sir? And then let's talk.
你病了吗  你的声音有点哑
Are you sick? You sound hoarse.
没有  我没生病
Well, no, I'm not sick.
只是缺觉而已
I haven't slept much.
好吧  我明天再给你打电话
All right, I'll call you tomorrow.
先生
Sir?
不好意思  先生
Excuse me. Sir?
我忘了我进来干什么了
I forgot why I came in here.
那瓶橙汁
The orange juice.
2美元25美分
That'll be two twenty-five.
好的
Yeah.
"国庆节已经变得毫无意义
"The Fourth of July means nothing anymore.
烤焦的热狗
Overcooked hot dogs
永远令你失望的焰火
and fireworks that always leave you disappointed.
中国制造的小号美国国旗
Bite-size American flags made in China,
在一心只想去打游戏的五岁顽童
halfheartedly waved by five-year-olds
手中有一搭没一搭地挥舞着
who'd rather be playing Minecraft.
但9月3日  却是真正重要的一天
But the third of September, that's a date which matters.
三十年前的这一天
It's the day, three decades past,
一个加夫尼的农民娶到了一位达拉斯的名媛
that a redneck from Gaffney married a debutante from Dallas.
世界旋转的角度在那天改变了
And the Earth's axis tilted that day,
尽管当时他们  以及我们都并不知道
though neither they, nor we, knew it at the time.
一个是将自己的婚誓比作
Here's a woman who describes her vows
在桥边为自杀而犹豫徘徊的女人
as a suicide flirting with a bridge's edge.
一个是将婚戒当作羞耻徽章的男人
And a man who wears his wedding ring as a badge of shame,
因为他觉得配不上这位名媛
for the debutante deserved more.
但是说真的  有夫如此  妇复何求
But truly, what more could she desire?
他们携手统治了一个没有子嗣的帝国
Together, they rule an empire without heirs.
遗志是他们唯一的孩子"
Legacy is their only child."
进来
Come in.
他也寄了一份给你
He sent you a copy, too?
我以为这书是关于你的  而不是我们
I thought this was supposed to be about you, not us.
这一切就是个错误
The whole thing was a mistake.
我们暴露太多了  弗兰西斯
We revealed too much, Francis.
我不该把你置于那种境地
I should've never put you in that position.
我会让这事到此为止
I'll put an end to it.
你觉得他说得对吗
Do you think he was right?
关于什么
About what?
"两个通用元素冷聚变
"A cold fusion of two universal elements,
重量一致  力量均等
identical in weight, equal in force.
他们站在一起  独一无二的联盟
United they stand. A union like none other.
成为美国政坛不可分裂的原子"
The unsplittable atom of American politics."
他总算说对一点
Well, he was right about some things.
我应该跟他面谈  减轻对他的打击
I should go speak to him face to face, soften the blow.
她昨天在奥维恩有活动
She did an event in Oelwein yesterday
我们的人说
and our people say you
欢呼声太大  几乎听不见她说话
could barely hear her with all the cheering.
她会对我们造成多大伤害
How badly can she hurt us?
他们只需要多一两个百分点  而且还没算上误差
They only need a point or two and he's in the margin of error.
所以我们得攻击她
So we need to attack her.
联合国的事没有攻击力  我们得想点新的
The UN stuff slid right off. We need something new.
跟杰姬谈谈
Let's talk to Jackie.
谢谢你能来  旅行顺利吗
Thank you for coming. How was your trip?
我还不错  但我妈受了点苦
Good for me. A little rough for my mom, though.
她不习惯连续两天看到我
She's not used to seeing me more than two days in a row.
她都没问题问我了
She actually ran out of questions.
我好嫉妒  坐吧  我一直忙个不停
I'm jealous. Have a seat. It's been nonstop here for me.
这边要轮轴转
Full-time job here.
还要代表希瑟去加州
Doing surrogate appearances for Heather in California.
我们真的很需要你  雷米
We could really use you, Remy.
这是招聘会面吗
A recruiting session?
你也该想到了吧
You can't be surprised.
我还希望你只是想看看我
I was hoping you just wanted to see my face.
我们无法向你提供格兰顿-希尔那样的薪酬
We can't offer you as much as you made at Glendon Hill,
但我们能比白宫给的多得多
but we can offer you a lot more than you made at the White House.
我没兴趣
I'm not interested.
回答得太快了吧  即便是对你来说
That was fast. Even for you.
-你去哪了  -没去哪
- Where'd you land? - Nowhere.
我退出了  杰姬  不再参与政治
I'm out, Jackie. No more politics.
你不是说真的  你就是干政治的
You know you don't mean that. It's who you are.
我以前很长一段时间也这么认为
That's what I thought, too, for a long time.
我都不知道还要不要待在华府
I don't even know if I'll stay in DC.
那你怎么打算
What are you gonna do?
这就是最棒的地方  我完全不知道
That's the best part. I have no idea.
你就别费劲说服我了
I'll save you the trouble of trying to convince me.
克莱尔·安德伍德
Claire Underwood.
我们必须狠狠打击她
We need to hit her hard.
你想要把柄  我没有
You want dirt. I don't have any.
你肯定有
You must.
如果我真有  我不知道我会不会给你
If I did, I don't know if I'd shovel it your way.
但我没有  他们从不让我进核心圈子
But I don't. They never let me in the inner circle.
她逼问过他  但毫无结果
She pressed him, but nothing.
我们竟然找不到
I find it hard to believe
一点把柄  真是难以置信
that we don't have a single thing we can use.
对手研究团队已经翻遍过去25年的
Our OPPO team has looked at every article,
每篇文章  每卷录像带
every piece of footage going back 25 years.
调查过所有熟人  家人  全套
Researched acquaintances, family, the works.
如果真的有  我们早找到了
If it's out there, we would've found it.
等等  还有一件事
Wait. There is one thing.
什么
What?
喂
Hello?
道格  好久没联系了
Doug. It's been a while.
-你想要什么  -那份日记
- What do you want? - The journal.
你要什么价
What would it take?
你说你永远不会那样对一个女人
You said you would never do that to another woman.
-要多少钱  -你要给我钱吗
- How much? - You're offering money?
如果这是你想要的
If that's what you want.
要我背叛别人可不便宜
Betrayal doesn't come cheap.
说个数字吧
Name a figure.
你喜欢看什么书
What do you like to read?
平时看书吗
Do you read?
我看的
Yes, I read.
谢谢  密查姆
Oh, thank you, Meechum.
-你不喜欢  -我没那么说
- You hate it. - I didn't say that.
你不会专程从爱荷华飞回来夸我
You wouldn't fly back from Iowa just to say, "Good job."
你刚给我21页
Well, look, you've only turned in 21 pages,
而那书本来现在就该完成了
and the book was supposed to be finished by now.
我花了这么久才想清楚究竟该写什么
It took me this long to figure out what the book is really about.
它应该写的  是你们俩
And what it's about, is the two of you.
我们得重新开始
We have to start over.
重新开始
Start over?
书应该是写《美国就业法案》的
The book was supposed to be about America Works.
你跟我说想尝试不同的角度
Now, you said you wanted to try a different approach.
我有怀疑  但支持了你  如今
I was skeptical, but then I went along with it and now,
你给了我一本书的开篇...
you've handed over to me the beginning of a book...
还是写我的婚姻的
about my marriage?
你想要我写得快  还是写得好
Well, do you want it fast, or do you want it right?
我跟你说过我从没在一年内写完一本书
I told you I've never written anything in less than a year.
对  再过一个月
Yeah, and in a month's time,
你又会说有了新想法
you're gonna say you've come up with some new idea.
不  就是这个了  你和克莱尔
No, this is it. You and Claire.
你们的婚姻
The marriage.
那是开启其他一切的关键
That's the key that unlocks everything else.
如果我想要曝光我的私人生活
If I had wanted an exposé about my personal life,
就从《美国周刊》雇个撰稿人来了
I would've hired a staff writer from Us Weekly.
等等  这不是小报的垃圾
Well... hold on a minute. This is not tabloid bullshit.
在这屋里  你说  你想要独特的声音
You said, in this room, you wanted an original voice.
我就在给你那个
I am giving it to you.
你不是思维狭隘的人  总统先生
You're not narrow-minded, Mr. President.
我知道你能理解我在做的事
I know you can appreciate what I'm trying to do.
是的  但你看  这就是问题
Right, but see, that's the problem right there.
这重点是你想做的事
This is about what you're trying to do.
是你的需求和...你怎么说的来着
What your needs and... what did you call it?
-你的瘾  -不是那样的
- Your addiction. - That's not true.
不  就是这样  我雇你来完成任务
No, it is true. I hired you to do a job,
就是帮我拉到选票
which was to get me votes.
早就该做到了  而不是六个月后
Yesterday, not six months from now.
这不是什么大事  这事没成功
Now, look, it's no big deal. It didn't work out.
但我保证  会付你全款
But I promise you, you will be paid in full.
谢谢你  汤姆
Thank you, Tom.
这书应该写完  应该被人读到
This deserves to be finished, and it deserves to be read.
我恰好不同意
Well, I just happen to disagree with you.
你害怕我写的东西吗
Are you afraid of what I wrote?
害怕  不
Afraid? No.
这只是不关其他人的事
It's just no one's business.
你不能埋没它
Well, you can't bury it.
我不会允许
I won't allow that.
你正在跟凯特·鲍德温拍拖
You're in an intimate relationship with Kate Baldwin,
对吗
isn't that correct?
我从没提过这事  因为我相信
I've never said anything because I presume that you can
你可以把个人生活跟我们的专业协议分开
separate your personal life from our professional arrangement.
但在你考虑一些轻率的主意前
But before you start getting any reckless ideas,
不如先记住一件事  这本书是我的
why don't you just remember one thing: I own this material.
如果你想跟任何人分享它
And if you attempt to share it with anybody,
哪怕是一个字
and I mean one single word,
诉讼算是最轻的麻烦了
litigation will be the least of your worries.
毕竟  我想我们都不愿意
I mean, after all, I don't think either of us
看到你第一本书的作者问题出现争议
wants any controversy about the authorship of your first book.
对吧
Do we?
密查姆  送耶茨先生出去好吗
Meechum, will you please escort Mr. Yates out?
祝你好运  汤姆
And good luck to you, Tom.
书的事真遗憾
Too bad about the book.
你不是真那么想
You don't really mean that.
没错
No, I don't.
格雷森先生来电  先生
Mr. Grayson is on the line, sir.
你说什么
What was that?
格雷森先生来电  先生  他说是急事
Mr. Grayson is on the line, sir. He says it's urgent.
他在1号线上  先生
He's on line one, sir.
赛斯
Seth?
好的  我最好待在华盛顿
All right. I better stay in Washington.
告诉沃恩
Let Vaughn know.
给我接克莱尔
Get me Claire.
你觉得宣布时机是算计好的
You think the timing is strategic?
他和邓巴关系很好
Well, he and Dunbar are close.
你对提名谁有想法吗
Do you have any idea who you're going to nominate?
我们明早会过一遍总名单
We'll go through our master list in the morning,
但这会让我无法按计划做宣传
but this'll take me off the campaign trail.
我一两天内还不能去爱荷华  你能替我吗
I won't be in Iowa for a day or two. You're okay to cover me?
当然可以  我会继续挥舞捧花
Yes, of course. I'll keep waving my pom-poms.
你能单独宣传真是个圣人
Well, you're a saint to do it without me,
但也许这样更好
but it's probably best.
他们更喜欢你
They like you even better.
你跟汤姆谈过了吗
Did you speak with Tom?
谈了  他不太乐意  但我说得很明确
I did. He didn't take it well, but I made it very clear.
我又看了一遍那一章
I read it again. The chapter.
别管了  我们摆脱他了
Let it go. We're done with him.
克莱尔
Claire?
抱歉  上场活动持续了很久
Sorry. Uh, the last event went quite long.
我累坏了
I'm fading.
你休息吧  明天再说
Well, you get some sleep. We'll talk tomorrow.
好  晚安  弗兰西斯
Okay. Good night, Francis.
晚安
Good night.
真是惊喜
This is a nice surprise.
时机不对吗
Now a bad time?
不会  你怎么进来的
Not at all. How did you get in the building?
没人通知我
Nobody called me.
接待员最喜欢的书是《天蝎》
The receptionist. Scorpio is her favorite book.
当然啦
Of course, it is.
在忙什么呢
What are you working on?
约旦河谷的机密行动
Covert operation in the Jordan Valley.
你老板安德伍德既不承认也不否认
Your boy Underwood has refused to confirm or deny,
但你看看这个
but take a look at that.
这是写给贾斯汀·尼克斯家人的信
That's a letter to the family of Justin Nix.
机密行动当天死亡的海豹突击队队员
Navy SEAL who died the same day as the covert operation.
总统签了字
Signed by the president.
上面写他在演练中丧生
Says it was a training exercise.
我刚跟国防部的线人通了电话
I just got off the phone with a source in the DOD
他们说当天没有海豹突击队演练
and they said there were no SEAL training exercises that day.
而10月18日
His death is the only
只报告了他一人阵亡
military KIA reported on October eighteenth.
我是不是打破你对他的美好幻想了
Am I shattering your illusions about the guy?
他炒了我
He fired me.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
我不想给你发邮件
I didn't want to e-mail it to you.
你的书
This is it?
第一章
The first chapter.
雅各布斯法官尽职尽责地服务了国家
Justice Jacobs served our nation with duty and distinction.
当法院意见不一致时
And when the Court was strongly divided,
在他任职的23年里  他数次
as it was many times during his 23 years on the bench,
凭自己的关键票
it was his swing vote
创造了流传后世的法律判例
that created legal precedents that will last for centuries.
虽然替任者很难找  但我一定会找到
Now, it will not be an easy seat to fill, but fill it I must.
先生
Sir.
邓巴的人刚联系我
Dunbar's people just reached out to me.
她回华盛顿了  想见你
She's back in Washington and she wants to meet with you.
干什么
What for?
她想谈法官提名的事
She wants to talk about the nomination.
她想推荐人
She wants to propose someone.
没错  她自己
Yes. Herself.
找个时间  找个隐秘的地方
Find a time. And find somewhere discreet.
别让任何在职人员看到她
I don't want anyone on staff seeing her.
早上好  我是克莱尔·安德伍德
Good morning. I'm Claire Underwood.
我刚给她换了尿布
Uh, I just changed her diaper.
还没来得及洗手
I haven't had a chance to wash my hands.
她叫什么  她好漂亮
What is her name? She's beautiful.
-凯拉  -凯拉  你叫什么
- Kayla. - Kayla. And what's your name?
-苏茜  -你好  苏茜
- Suzie. - Hi, Suzie.
我只想感谢你的支持
Well, I just wanted to thank you so much for your support.
对我丈夫和我意义重大
It means so much to my husband and me.
我不支持他
I don't support him.
我看到了外面的标志
I saw the signs out front.
那是我丈夫的  我支持希瑟·邓巴
Those are my husband's. I support Heather Dunbar.
我们来踩点时  她丈夫在
When we vetted the house, the husband was here.
你会考虑改变想法吗
Um, would you ever consider changing your mind?
抱歉  安德伍德夫人
I'm sorry, Mrs. Underwood,
我不想上电视或报纸
I don't really want to be on TV or in the papers.
抱歉
My apologies about that.
介意我进去坐坐吗
Would you mind if I just came inside?
不拍照  只有我
No cameras, just me?
应该可以吧
I guess so.
我们得先排查这间房子  夫人
We need to do a sweep of the house first, ma'am.
不用  他们留在外面
No. And they stay out here.
你好  希瑟
Hello, Heather.
罗伯特怎么样
How's Robert?
他很难过
He's sad.
但他至少能体面地退出
But at least he's making his exit with grace.
你在新闻发布会上
Those were some very nice things
说他的话很不错
you said about him during your press conference.
你之前怎么跟我说的
Well, what was it you said to me...
要把什么说成好听的
about, uh, making things palatable?
-不堪的目的  -没错  不堪
- The obscene. - Ah, yes. The obscene.
的确是不堪  他这么好的头脑不再灵活
Well, it is obscene, a mind like his losing its sharpness.
我不指望去总统办公室  但这...有意思
I didn't expect the Oval, but this is interesting.
这是我和佩特罗夫在峰会时抽雪茄的地方
This is where Petrov and I smoked cigars during the summit.
这是他在墙上戳灭烟头的地方
That's where he put his out on the wall.
赛斯跟我说你想要法官提名
So, Seth tells me you want the nomination.
不  我是为了进门才那么说
No. I just said that to get in the door.
罗伯特认为如果这意味着我退出竞选
Robert thought you'd say yes in a heartbeat
你会立刻答应
if it meant me dropping out of the race.
但是退不退出
But the decision you have to make
是你要做的决定
is whether you'll drop out or not.
我为什么要那么做呢
And why would I do that?
我知道克莱尔在流产一事上撒了谎
I know Claire lied about the abortion,
我也有日记作为证据
and I have the journal to prove it.
我是在给你体面退出的机会
I'm giving you an opportunity to bow out gracefully,
就像罗伯特那样
just like Robert.
但是你要在党团会议之前退出
But you have to do it before the caucus.
我给你三天时间
I'll give you three days.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
就是你让道格销毁的那本
The one you asked Doug to destroy.
他或许没有照做
I wouldn't be so certain that he did it.
那么...
So...
你终于也变成我们这种人了
you're finally one of us.
什么人
One of who?
待在烟雾缭绕的密室里的男人
The men. In their smoky back rooms.
如果日记真的存在
And even if there was a journal...
你也没这个种
you don't have it in you.
随便你怎么想
Make whatever assumption you want.
罗伯特是对的  我会把提名给你
Well, Robert was right. I would offer you the nomination.
你应该采纳睿智之人的建议
You should take the advice of a smart man.
三天  总统先生
Three days, Mr. President.
想想克莱尔
Think about Claire.
请送我出去
Show me out, please.
她怎么冲我来都可以
She can go after me all she wants,
可她敢找克莱尔的麻烦
but she goes after Claire,
我就在光天化日之下割了她喉咙
I'll slit her fucking throat in broad daylight.
他赦免了沃克  还有那个有钱人
Like when he pardoned Walker, and that other guy, the rich one.
-雷蒙德·塔斯克  -对  就是他
- Raymond Tusk. - Yeah, him.
他们是坏人  结果却被他放走了
I mean, those were bad people, and he let them off the hook.
还有  他说不参选  结果还是参选了
And then he says he's not running and he does.
这个嘛  比你说的
Well, it's a little more complicated
要更复杂一些
than the way you're putting it.
有很多因素
There's a lot of variables
导致他做出那样的决策
that go into making decisions like that, and...
那时我就在他身边  我知道他多痛苦
I can tell you I was right beside him and he was agonizing.
抱歉  她饿了
I'm sorry. She's hungry.
我还在给我女儿喂奶
I still breastfeed my girl.
-请回避一下  -夫人
- Go outside, please. - Ma'am?
出去一下就好
Just go outside.
你要是希望的话  我也可以回避
I can go out too, if you like.
不必了
No, it's okay.
只要你不介意看到我的胸
As long as you don't mind seeing some boob.
她有兄弟姐妹吗
Does she have any brothers or sisters?
没有  她是独生女
No, this is the only one.
詹姆斯和我努力了好一阵儿
James and I have been trying for a while.
我一直怀不上
Had some trouble getting pregnant.
-詹姆斯是你丈夫  -是  他叫吉姆
- James is your husband? - Yeah. He goes by Jim.
但我更喜欢叫他詹姆斯
But I like James better.
他肯定是信任我丈夫的  毕竟他支持他
Well, he must trust my husband. He's supporting him.
詹姆斯都不知道那个词什么意思
James doesn't know what that word means.
-信任吗  -对  整个镇子都知道
- Trust? - Yeah. The whole town knows it.
只要是女人他都追
He runs after anything in a skirt.
说实在话  我不怎么介意
Which I don't mind so much, to be honest.
我自己也放纵过几回
I mean, I've had a fling or two myself.
我不喜欢他为此撒谎
What I don't like is how he lies about it.
然后  当他问我有没有另找过
And then, when he asks me if I've been with someone
而我说有的时候  他就气得发疯
and I say yes, he flips out.
就好像存在双重标准似的
Like there's some kind of double standard.
他想在克里斯蒂·莫利根
I mean, he wants to dog Christy Mulligan
新车的后座上跟她后入式
in the back of her brand new Escalade?
行啊  那为什么我就不能为凯拉的婴儿床
Fine. Why shouldn't I be able to give Kyle Beckenbauer some head
给凯尔·贝肯鲍尔吹箫致谢呢
for building Kayla's crib?
不好意思
I'm sorry.
这就是三个月不睡的结果
This is what happens when you don't sleep for three months.
你们两口子打架吗  你和你丈夫
You two fight? You and your husband?
每对已婚夫妇都吵架的
Every married couple fights.
我是指真正的打架  能把警察招来那种
I mean, really fight. Like, the cops get called.
或者说  他要不是总统  警察就会来那种
Or they would, if he wasn't the president.
因为
'Cause I mean,
治安官如今几乎是我们家一员了
the sheriff is practically a family member at this point.
现在我们又为这该死的选举打架
Now we're fighting about the damn election.
比如院子里那些破标语
Like those stupid yard signs.
有时候我真希望能收拾东西离开他
Sometimes, I wish I could just pull up stakes and leave him.
但是我做不到  为什么呢
But I can't. Why not?
因为这个小家伙
Because of this little one.
我们最后一次做试管婴儿时  我对自己说
Last in vitro we did, I said to myself,
如果这次还不行  我就走人
if this one doesn't work, I'm outta here.
我们为了要孩子把房子二次抵押了
We had to double mortgage the house to pay for it.
但好使了  于是就这样了
But it worked. And... here I am.
如果我像你  没孩子
If I was like you... didn't have a kid...
能告诉你个秘密吗
Can I tell you a secret?
没有哪个母亲会承认  但有时候我幻想
No mother will admit this, but sometimes I fantasize,
用这块枕头...
like, like this pillow here...
趁凯拉在摇篮里的时候
I mean, and when Kayla was in her crib.
就两分钟就行  我就能离开了
Two minutes. That's all it would take, and I could go.
我不用留在一个我想离开的男人身边
And I wouldn't be stuck to a man I want to leave,
往乳头上抹乳液  好让它软
rubbing lotion on my nipples, they're so raw.
我可以重新开始
I could start over.
当然  我不是真那么想  我绝不会那么做
Of course, I don't mean it. I mean, I'd never to do that.
但...人会胡思乱想
But... you have thoughts.
苏茜
You know what, Suzie,
我觉得我占用你太多时间了
I think I've taken up too much of your time.
你知道我不是真那么想吧
You know I'm not serious, right?
当然
Of course.
抱歉  我就是...
I'm sorry. I'm just...
好累啊
I'm so tired.
你真是个好倾听者
You're a really good listener.
真希望你能去竞选总统
I wish you were running for president.
如果你想可以告诉他们我支持你丈夫
Hey, you can tell them I'm for your husband if you want.
我大概都不会参加党团会议
I probably won't even caucus.
祝你好运  苏茜
Good luck to you, Suzie.
安德伍德夫人  她改主意了吗
Mrs. Underwood, did she change her mind?
没有  她坚持己见
No, she stuck to her guns.
但你不能怪一个女人坚持信念
But you can't blame a woman for having conviction.
总统刚刚打来找您
The president just called for you.
我上车后给他打回去
I'll call him back from the car.
听我说  我要告诉你件事  你别慌
Listen to me. What I'm about to say, I don't want you to panic.
怎么了
What is it?
日记  邓巴说在她手里
The journal. Dunbar claims she has it.
-怎么会  -我不知道
- But how? - I don't know.
看来可能是道格
It looks like it might have been Doug.
-他不是...  -我知道  我也难以置信
- He was supposed to-- - I know. It's hard for me to believe.
不  弗兰西斯  这绝不行
No, Francis. This can't happen.
密查姆正在找他
Meechum is tracking him down now.
亲爱的  听我说
Sweetheart, listen to me.
不  这件事...这件事
No, the whole thing, it-- The whole thing--
她只是威胁了我
All she did was make the threat.
她未必真会那么做
That doesn't mean she actually has it.
不论如何  解决这事  弗兰西斯
Whatever you have to do. Just fix it, Francis.
我会的  我保证
I will, I promise you that.
但是现在  你得回来
But in the meantime, you have to come back here.
你得上飞机  你得回来
I need you to get to the plane. You have to come back.
如果我们被奇袭了  我不希望你还在外面
I don't want you there, out on the road, if we get blindsided.
克莱尔  克莱尔
Claire? Claire.
我这就回去
I'll come home.
马上登机  就说你不舒服
You go straight to the plane. We'll say you weren't feeling well.
好
Okay.
上帝  让我平静接受我无法改变的事
God, grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change,
让我勇敢改变我可以改变的事
the courage to change the things I can,
并拥有分辨二者的智慧
and the wisdom to know the difference.
坚持来  如果有帮助  就继续努力
Keep coming back. It works if you work it.
怎么样
So?
你还真以为他会喜欢这个吗
You honestly believed he'd go for this?
是啊
Yeah.
内容很好  而且很坦诚
The writing is good. And it's honest.
但哪个神经正常的候选人
But what candidate in their right mind
会希望这样的东西发表啊
would want something like this out there?
我要你报导出去  他想扼杀这本书
I need you to write about it. That he's trying to suppress this.
-你需要的是睡眠  -帮帮我吧  凯特
- What you need is sleep. - Do this for me, Kate.
-不行  这有利益冲突  -得了
- I can't. It's a conflict of interest. - Come on.
我们一上床  就越界了
The moment we slept together, we crossed the line.
去他的界线
Fuck the line!
我不能因为你的书没戏就赌上我的名誉
I'm not risking my reputation because your book is dead.
不  还有戏呢
Oh, no. Not dead.
我会写完的
I'm gonna finish it.
如果有必要  我会改掉名字  当成小说
I'll change the names if I have to, call it fiction.
他是美国总统
He's the President of the United States.
-那又如何  -他能毁掉别人
- So what? - He crushes people.
放手吧  重新开始
Let this go. Just start something new.
"重新开始"
"Start something new."
天呐  你根本不懂
Jesus... Christ, you don't get it.
我经常这样
I do it all the time.
我的编辑毙掉一篇报导  我继续做下一篇
My editor passes on a story, I move on to the next one.
我现在对你太他妈失望了
I'm so fucking disappointed in you right now.
我吗
Me?
我是想把你从幻想中拯救出来
I'm the one trying to save you from your own delusions.
他就是这么说的
That's exactly what he said.
也许他说得对
Maybe he's right.
我都快对你有感情了
I almost felt something for you.
进来吧
Come in.
外套给我吧
Let me take your coat.
要给你拿点什么吗  拿点喝的
Can I get you anything? Something to drink?
不不  不用  谢谢
No. No, I'm good. Thanks.
多谢你来我家  但我不会改变主意的
I appreciate the home visit, but I'm not gonna change my mind.
不不  我没觉得你会改主意
No, no. I didn't think you would.
出什么事了吗
Something wrong?
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know what to do.
我以为
I figured...
我邀你加入竞选时
when I asked you to join the campaign,
我以为你会答应
I just assumed you would say yes.
我们就可以一起工作
That the two of us, we would be working together.
而且
And...
我...我
I... I...
我无法停止想你
I can't stop thinking about you.
你结婚了  杰姬
You're married, Jackie.
因为错误的原因
For the wrong reasons.
我以为你们彼此相爱
I thought you loved each other.
不是这种爱
Not like this.
我没做我想做的人
I'm not the person I want to be.
你做了你应该做的  看看你的成就
You're who you need to be. Look at what you've achieved.
但你做到了  你彻底放弃了
But you did it. You gave it all up.
毫不犹豫
In a heartbeat.
我们是不同的人
We're different people.
你该走了
You should go.
把这些抛在脑后
Put this behind you.
看来以为我们依能保持亲密是我天真了
I guess it was naive to think that we could remain close.
到此为止了吗
So this is it?
是的  到此为止了
Yeah. It is.
杰姬
Jackie?
Jackie...
她说在她那儿
She says she has it.
她撒谎
She doesn't.
我怎么知道没有其它副本
How do I know there aren't other copies?
你的烟放在哪
Where do you keep your cigarettes?
在那上面的碗里
In the bowl up there.
我当初让你销毁时  你为什么不销毁
Why didn't you destroy it when I first asked you to?
不知道
I don't know.
有什么阻止了我  也许有一天我会用到
Something stopped me. Maybe I would need it one day.
为了你  证明我的忠诚
For you. To prove my loyalty.
你告诉她了  我可没法称之为忠诚
You told her. I'd hardly call that loyalty.
我得向她表明我是认真的
I had to show her I was serious.
这份日记就能证明
The journal was a way to do that.
我从没想过把日记交给她
I never came close to putting it in her possession.
我还要知道什么吗
Anything else I should know?
我戒酒了  已经87天了
I'm sober. It's been 87 days.
我是说关于邓巴
I meant in regards to Dunbar.
这是有关的  现在双方势均力敌
It is related. This is a tight race.
让我做你的幕僚长
Make me your Chief of Staff.
你保证过的
You promised.
你保证等我准备好了  这里会有我一席之地
You promised there'd be a place for me here when I was ready.
那是在你旧瘾复发
That was before you fell off the wagon
拿着日记走进来之前
and walked in here with that journal.
我犯过错
I've made mistakes.
我不止一次跌倒
I've fallen down more than once,
而你总会扶我起来
and you've always been there to pick me up.
但过去一年  你也不断跌倒
But you've been falling down for the past year, too,
这次你需要一个人来扶你
and you need someone to pick you up this time.
不是雷米  不是赛斯
It's not Remy. It's not Seth.
是我  弗兰克
It's me, Frank.
我怎么知道我能再次信任你呢
And how can I know I can ever trust you again?
因为我刚刚烧掉了两百万美元
Because I just lit two million dollars on fire.
到会人数可能比以往多  在180到220之间
We expect higher than usual turnout, anywhere from 180 to 220.
人越多越好
The higher the turnout, the better.
我们在女性和学生中较受欢迎
We're stronger with women and students.
-我们已争取到...  -抱歉  我得接这通电话
- We've got a GOTV-- - Excuse me, I have to take this.
道格
Doug?
关于日记  我有新消息要告诉你
I have an update regarding the journal.
是什么
What is it?
来自总统的口信
A message from the president.
我只有一件事要说
I have only one thing to say.
去你妈的
Go fuck yourself.
天呐  感觉太棒了
Christ, that felt good.
列一份最高法院的
Start putting together a shortlist
人选名单
of potential nominees for the court.
你已经...
You already...?
有我呢  先生
I'm on it, sir.
克莱尔
Claire.
要我叫楼下厨房
Want me to have them make you something
给你做点什么吗
from the downstairs kitchen?
不用  我在机上吃了  就是有点热
No, I ate on the plane. Just feeling a little warm.
会过去的
It'll pass.
道格怎么说
What did Doug say?
已经销毁了
It's destroyed.
我亲眼看他烧的
I watched him burn the page myself.
-有副本吗  -他说没有
- What about copies? - He says there aren't any.
你信任他吗
And you trust him?
他有的是机会搞破坏  但他没有
He had ample opportunity to do us real damage and he didn't.
-但他留了那么久  -我信他  克莱尔
- But he held onto it for so long-- - I believe him, Claire.
我信他
I believe him.
我要让他做幕僚长
And I'm gonna make him my Chief of Staff.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我们需要他  克莱尔  如今更甚以往
We need him, Claire. We need him now more than ever.
他背叛了我们  弗兰西斯
He betrayed us, Francis!
他把我的事告诉了邓巴
He told Dunbar about me.
是为了赢得她的信任  不是为了背叛我们
To gain her trust, not betray ours.
听我说  道格是我们一直以来唯一能信任的人
Look, Doug is the only person we've ever been able to trust,
而且他这次手段很高明
and he played this very smart.
他从未真的让我们有危险
He never put us in any real danger.
日记已经销毁  她做不了什么
The journal is gone. She can't do anything.
你让他回来之前  为什么不跟我商量
Why didn't you ask me before you brought him back?
-我们这不在商量吗  -你已经雇了他
- Bec-- We're discussing it now. - After you hired him!
听我说  我知道这事让你很揪心
Look. I know this must have been harrowing for you,
-但听我说  都结束了  -不  我不...
- but listen, it is ov-- - No. I don't--
我开始质疑一切了  弗兰西斯
I'm starting to question all of it, Francis.
这一切究竟有什么意义  我们这么做是为了什么
What any of it is worth. What... what are we doing this for?
为了这栋房子
For this house.
为了总统之位
For the presidency.
听我说  如果你需要休息几天  那没什么
Now, look, if you need to take a few days off, that's fine.
你明天不用跟我去爱荷华州
You do not have to come with me to Iowa tomorrow.
不  我当然要去
No. Of course, I'll be there.
欢迎回来  道格  恭喜了
Welcome back, Doug. Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
我只想问下你打算
I just wanted to get a heads up on
什么时候正式宣布
when you'd like to make the formal announcement.
党团会议之后吧
Let's do it after the caucus.
不要让大家的注意力偏离竞选
I don't want to draw any attention away from the campaign.
那你今天别参加新闻发布会了
You probably shouldn't attend the press briefing today.
嗯  我会在那之前走的
No. I'll take off before then.
给  你该看看
Here, you should see this.
10分钟前曝出的
This just came out ten minutes ago.
你给总统看了吗
Have you shown the president?
我起草了讲话要点
I drafted up some talking points.
我觉得你会想去跟他说
I figured you'd want to brief him.
我回办公室了
I'll be in my office.
赛斯
Seth.
总统告诉我你也想做这工作
The president told me you asked for the job.
我当时不知道你也有这打算
Yeah, I didn't realize that you were in contention.
我不希望你怨我
I don't want you to resent me.
我是专业人士的
Hey, I'm a professional.
你如果要改讲话要点告诉我
Let me know if you want any changes made to the talking points.
肯定写的很好
I'm sure they're good.
拿去给总统吧
You can share 'em with the president.
你不要先过目吗
You don't want to look 'em over first?
不用  我相信你
No. I trust your judgment.
我可以告诉大家  名单正在筹办
I can tell you that the shortlist is coming along,
我有意在接下来两三周里
and it is my intention to nominate someone
就做出提名
within the next two or three weeks.
我们一定要行动快
It's very important that we do this quickly,
让参议院有时间进行听证
so that the Senate has time for their hearings.
这个位置本来也不好空太久
And we shouldn't leave that seat empty too long anyway,
法庭还要继续运行
while the Court is still in session.
-总统  -萨拉
- Mr. President? - Sara.
总统先生  您能就鲍德温女士关于
Mr. President, would you comment on Ms. Baldwin's article
约旦河谷行动的文章做下评论吗
about the Jordan Valley operation?
我觉得鲍德温女士的文章
I think Ms. Baldwin's article
不过是臆测
is really nothing more than speculation.
-但是证据  -什么
- But the evidence... - I'm sorry?
但她提出的证据很有说服力
But the evidence she presents is convincing.
证据  一封信吗
Evidence? A letter?
很遗憾  我虽不愿意
Unfortunately, I have to write letters like that
却不得不常写这种信
more often than I would like.
我觉得这仅仅能证明
And I don't think it's proof of anything more than
我曾写信给一个为国捐躯的
I reached out to the family of a young man
年轻人的家人
who sacrificed his life for our country
以及我对此永远充满谢意
and for which I am eternally grateful.
总统先生
Mr. President?
鲍德温女士  我们讨论的是你的文章
Well, Ms. Baldwin, it is your article we're discussing.
我想如果我不让你提问
I suppose I'd get hammered
恐怕会挨批评
if I didn't allow you to ask a question.
谢谢  总统先生  我的问题很简单
Thank you, Mr. President. My question is very straightforward.
您在信中提到
You mentioned in the letter
尼可斯中尉在演练中丧命
that Lieutenant Nix died in a training exercise.
您亲自在信上签名
You signed this letter with your own hand.
您能如实告诉我们他是这么死的吗
Can you tell us in all honesty that this is how he died?
我要告诉你
I can tell you that
这就是五角大楼向我报告的情况
this is exactly what the Pentagon reported to me.
除此之外  政府和国防部
And beyond that, it's not the policy of this administration
都不会讨论关于特种部队士兵
or the Department of Defense to discuss any specifics
死亡的详细情况
about any Special Forces deaths.
我能再问一个问题吗
May I ask one more, please?
我想这个话题已经讨论完了
I believe we're finished with that subject now.
是关于爱荷华
It's about Iowa.
好吧  问吧
Yes, all right. Go ahead.
您妻子出席了多场竞选活动
Your wife has been doing a lot of events.
她辞去在联合国的职位
Did she resign her post at the United Nations
是因为您觉得她作为竞选筹码
because you think she's more valuable as a campaign asset
比当大使更有价值吗
than an ambassador?
克莱尔确实出席了很多活动  这是事实
Claire has been doing a lot of events, that is true,
跟她以前参与我的每场竞选一样
as she has in every campaign that I have ever run.
我想我的策略是希望美国人民
I'm hoping, I suppose my strategy is that if the American people
看到我能凭聪明才智
can see that I was smart enough
娶到像克莱尔这样出色的女人
to marry an extraordinary woman like Claire,
他们或许会认为我也有
well, they might think I'm smart enough
当美国总统的脑子
to be President of the United States.
至于大使的事
As for the ambassadorship,
那完全是她的决定  不是我的
that was entirely her decision, not mine.
她喜欢竞选宣传  我也希望能今天稍后能
She enjoys campaigning, and I'm looking forward to getting back
回到爱荷华州陪伴她
to Iowa with her a little later today.
非常感谢各位
Thank you all very much.
我们知道他在加拉加斯[委瑞内拉首都]附近
We know he's somewhere near Caracas.
我需要找他回来
I need him back.
委瑞内拉方面不太配合
The Venezuelans haven't been cooperating.
我们有引渡令
We have extradition.
不代表他们会执行
Doesn't mean they'll enforce.
那就给我个准确地址
Then get me a precise location.
为什么
Why?
这跟你没关系
It doesn't concern you.
跟我有关  局里很多人
It does concern me. There are a lot of people
因为他的偷偷离境
at the agency who are embarrassed that
而丢了人
he crossed the border without us knowing.
那不是我的错
That's not my problem.
是你吗  护照解锁
Was it you? Passport lock?
能办到这事的再就只有国安部
The only other agency that could've lifted it is Homeland.
我知道你那里有朋友
I know you have friends there.
我到处都有朋友
I have friends everywhere.
我不会帮你擦屁股的  道格
I'm not gonna help you clean up your mess, Doug.
如果是你帮他出逃的话
Not if you helped him escape.
这不是请求
This isn't a request.
我现在是总统的幕僚长
I'm Chief of Staff to the president now.
-他还没宣布呢  -他会的
- He hasn't announced anyone. - He will.
如果你希望我的第一项正式工作
And if you want my first official task
就是找人代替你  那行啊
to be finding your replacement, so be it.
否则  就告诉我嘉文在哪
If not, you tell me where Gavin is.
我今早看了新闻发布会
I watched the press conference this morning.
我觉得鲍德温的文章会被淡忘的
I think the Baldwin article will blow over.
毫无力量  站不住脚
A non-story. No legs.
你说是我决定辞职的
You said it was my decision to resign.
确实是啊  不是吗
Well, it was, wasn't it?
至少我们是这样表现的
I mean, at least that's how we presented it.
我昨天在爱荷华跟一个女人聊天
I spoke with a woman yesterday in Iowa, who...
她说她不会支持我们
said she couldn't support us...
因为她不信任你
because she doesn't trust you.
我又不是第一个不被一些人信任的政客
Well, I'm not the first politician that some people don't trust.
我们已经撒谎很长时间了  弗兰西斯
We've been lying for a long time, Francis.
当然  想想如果我们开始说出真相
Of course we have. Imagine what the voters would think
选民会怎么想
if we started telling the truth.
不是对选民
Not to them.
是对彼此
To each other.
提名最高法院法官  往往是一名美国总统任内最重要的工作之一
由于美国最高法院法官是终身制
一旦获得任命  大法官就可以一直工作下去
一名总统最多只能在白宫发号施令8年
他所提名的大法官却可以在最高法院影响美国社会长达几十年
在寻找合适人选时  总统们会选择同自己政见相似的候选人
但是由于任职后没有选举压力
大法官们在判案时并不见得总会站在自己所属的党派一边
小布什总统在离任前提名共和党人约翰·罗伯兹为最高法院首席大法官
但是当民主党总统奥巴马的《医疗保险改革法案》遇到麻烦时
罗伯兹却把自己关键的一票投给了支持奥巴马的一方
目前在任的九名大法官中
已经82岁高龄的民主党人露丝·金士堡是年龄最长的一位
金士堡曾两次罹患癌症  虽然都已治愈  但是健康状况欠佳
许多民主党人都在劝她尽快退休
这样现任总统奥巴马就有机会提名一位民主党法官来取代她
一旦民主党在2016年大选中失手  被共和党人占了白宫
而金士堡在2016年后退休  就会被一名共和党人取而代之
打破最高法院现有的平衡
但是倔强的金士堡拒绝听取这些劝退的意见
她总是回答说  奥巴马不可能找到比我更好的人选
在过去连续两年的国情咨文演讲中  奥巴马在台上口若悬河
坐在台下的金士堡却在打盹儿
不久前她在接受访问时承认  今年参加国情咨文前
跟最高法院几位法官同僚喝了几杯  才会在会场上忍不住打盹儿